Mu Ying!
What did you do to Mu Ying?!
Jiang Huai.
You only have the burn time of an incense stick.
Find the vault's location in the book.
If you dare call the police,
I'll kill Mu Ying before time is up.
Mu Ying
The Old Newsvendor
Are you crazy? You dare tie me up?
I didn't want to hurt you,
but you kept hounding me.
Aren't you supposed to be so resourceful?
Poison gas will be released soon.
You won't last long.
I wonder if Jiang Huai
will solve the riddle in time.
Inspector Mu,
just enjoy yourself.
Don't go! Don't go!
Don't let me catch you!
Master,
let's get out of here.
This Lijia Town is too scary.
We almost died here.
No.
I have to save Mu Ying first.
Tell me the truth.
Why are you helping me?
Isn't it obvious?
Because my Master likes you.
Master!
What are you doing?
Wake up, Bookworm!
Master! Bookworm!
Master, wake up!
Master!
Look out!
Mu Ying has saved me so many times.
I absolutely can't leave her behind.
If you want to leave,
leave by yourself.
If you're not leaving,
then neither am I.
I was just a stinking beggar anyway.
You saved me by teaching me storytelling.
Old man,
I'll fight you to the death!
Rascal,
Well done!
Come,
write down everything I'm about to say.
Okay.
We can't just sit here and wait to die.
We need to find a way out, fast.
Open the door!
It's not heat-activated.
Nor is it written in white vinegar.
Why doesn't this book
have any clues to the vault's location?
Maybe this book
doesn't have the vault's location at all.
The old man is bluffing.
Jiang Huai!
You've already wasted 30 minutes.
The second wave of poison gas is coming!
Old man!
Don't go, old man!
What could this be?
Master.
Master!
There's a seal here.
A seal?
Fire Qilin.
It's a Late Qing Prince's collection mark.
Qilin...
Fire Qilin.
Fire...
I get it!
Master!
Did you find a clue?
The cipher for the vault's location...
shouldn't be too complicated.
It must be hidden within this mark.
This Qilin is the address.
The Fire Qilin is a mythical sacred beast.
It represents fortune and prosperity.
And it also represents treasure.
But this book is all about crafting methods.
There's no mention of a Qilin at all.
The Fire Qilin is just a hint.
What matters most is the word "fire."
In the book Heavenly Craftsmanship,
the sections that mention fire
are metallurgy
and casting techniques.
Look.
I was right.
"Whenever exposed to intense fire,
one quarter will be consumed."
This character for "four"...
is bolder than the regular text.
Write it down quickly.
Okay.
I get it.
If a sentence mentions "fire,"
any bolded character in it
is part of the vault's address.
"Apply external fire."
The "hua" in "carbonize its oil and wax,"
is also bolded.
Sihua Street, North Alley
Exactly.
is the location of the vault.
Old man!
Come out!
We found the address!
Take the book.
Old man!
We found it.
Speak.
Tell me now!
Where is the vault located?
Let Mu Ying go first,
then I'll tell you the vault's location.
If anything happens to her,
for as long as you live,
you'll never get the vault's address.
You think I'm negotiating with you?